Seeno, Galgal Channel, go-go!
Yes, so today I would like to do a tension manipulation dance.
Yes, I'm going to do two songs.
I'm going to do about two songs.
By the way, everyone has done this before, right?
Yes, we have.
It's been a long time ago, hasn't it?
That's the second time.
Yes, twice.
We have done it three times before.
This time, I would like to do it with this group.
Let's start the video!
I am wearing T-Holic's costume this time.
Yes, I'm wearing T-Holic's costume this time. Let's take a turn.
Let's start with the losers.
The winners first.
The first one is "goo" and the second one is "janken poi.
It's aiko, right? It's aiko, right? It's aiko, right? It's aiko, right?
Then, here is rock, paper, scissors.
Rock, paper, scissors.
Oh, let's play rock-paper-scissors-scissors.
Let's go to number 2.
Rock, paper, scissors.
We'll do it in this order.
The first song is choo-choo-choo.
It's choo-choo-choo.
Now let's start the music.
Oh, first shot.
Midnight.
Midnight tension.
No, intense.
I haven't seen much midnight footage.
Oh, so this is what it's like.
Oh, no.
That's what it looks like.
Hwang duo.
I can't remember how to pretend.
Can't move.
Looking backwards.
Still, you know.
It's over.
Weak.
Ah, it looks weak.
This is difficult.
It's difficult.
Here, look.
Oh, it's good.
I like it.
You're going all out.
It's good.
My face is too loud, so it's my gig.
That's nice.
It's good.
Your expression hurt.
Okay, Sasaki Sena.
Asahi.
Hi.
Oh, my.
Sexy.
She's an actor.
Oh, man.
You're an actor. You're a seducer.
You're an actor.
Sexy.
What?
What was it?
Yes.
I knew it was the face.
That's right.
I get a lot of hair shakes.
Overreaction.
Do they do this with their faces?
Dance.
Oh, wow.
Great.
Oh, my God.
Is it safe?
Safe.
Oh, no, no, no.
No, I think it's good.
It's too 16-bit limited.
Have you ever met anyone like that?
I don't know.
You never know.
Hey, sis.Sister.
She's my sister.
That's tough.
I can do it.
I'm fine.
Happy as can be.
You're so sharp.
Happy, happy, happy.
Good, good, good.
Just in case.
Yes.
It's always good to give it your all.
Brilliant.
Nice.
You're blicko.
It's still transforming.
Good night, Mr. *Ohkun.
Ouch! It hurts so much!
Ouch!
Continue!
You have a good eye line, don't you?
You're giving off a can-do vibe.
What can you do?
It's an audition.
Good luck.
You win.
You'll do great.
My stomach dropped.
Meow!
Go! Go! Go!
Is that it?
Let me do it, mom.
Let's hear it! Let's hear it!
It's not a dance.
Are you a friend of Grandpa's today?
That's nice.
I'll get the audition.
Grandpa!
Different moves! Different pose!
To me 4!
Reduce to n̶n̶e
Reduce to ̶n̶e̶e̶
Oh, this is hot.
No one is shy anymore, so no more million dollars.
Good, good, good.
One hundred points.
What do we do now? Next.
I want to do one more song.
One more song,
ENJOY.
Change the order?
The "determination" that you were talking about earlier.
Would you like to try the "Determination" method?
Actually, I'm not going to try the determination way,
O
Unknown.
A
B
A. Yes.
Yes.
Type AB.
I think it's a little awkward to say "unknown," so I'm going to ask you to dance here for a long time,
Then, let's dance in the order of ABO.
I understand.
Now we are in the middle of listening to the decision.
Type A.
Type A. Unknown. Type B. Type O.
Type B. Type O.
Basically, unknown is dancing all the time,
I will dance.
What does this really mean?
Catchy, it would be better if you go to the front.
I think I'll be in the center.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
Well then, I'd like to ENJOY.
Let the music begin!
Hey, hey, hey, hey, sexy.
Sexy.
Step on it, poor thing.
Step on it.
Step on it!
Come on.
Can you do it again?
Go, go, go, go, go!
Go, go, go, go!
What a waste!I just can't believe it.
I've always felt sorry for you
I can't dance anymore
I can't dance anymore.
Hey!
Laughter.
I'm gonna cry.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh no, Kakus!
Why, why, why...
Oh, oh, oh,
Yo-yo-shuku
It's a face game!
Just give me your face.
Put on live!
Live!
Live pop!
Oh, you're suddenly changing your side leg.
No, no, no, no, no.
GO!
Over, over. That's hard.
Hard, now, just a little bit.
All the way. All the way.
This is it, isn't it?
Oh, my God, why is it coming true?
Get mad. Get mad.
What was that?
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
I'm in trouble.
Please get angry. Your face is not angry.
Get angry!
It's too tight!
I can't use my strength.
What's what?
Hide it!
I'm nervous!
Hang in there!
You have to wear it!
Kindness!
Kitty cat!
Pussycat!
It's still inside.
Nah nah nah nah!
I'm working on it too.
Guest!
Appeal!
No?
Rumors.
Too gung-ho for you?
What?
It's got a touch of the ocean about it.
We're both in on it.
You're impossible.
Impossible girl.
Impossible child.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
Come on.
I don't want to smile.
I know, it's a face game.
I want to cry.
What's this?
This is pretty good.
Good, good, good.
You're trying too hard.
Can I make your voice funny?
I just left the hard stuff to you.
Thank you very much.
I'd love it if you did.
Karaoke.
It was perfect.
It was great.
What do you mean by MVP?
It was really good.
I am the MVP.
It's all the same for one person.
How do you feel?
I don't do it with a lot of emotions,
I think it was a very gratifying experience.
The level of professionalism is high.
I hope you will continue to express your emotions to us.
Thank you.
It was a great opportunity.
Thank you for watching.
If you liked this video,
If you liked this video, please subscribe to my channel, give me a high rating, and comment.
Bye-bye.Bye bye.
Please subscribe to our channel.